Mss.B.Al1 Mss.B.AL1
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Letter to Mr. Richards, March 15, [1847]; 10-1/2x8; Scott, Peter
    Printed L.S. 1p. (see Album 1, p.318.) Concerning the breeding of waterfowls in England.
  - Letter to Mr. Mulock, 5-1/2x4; Scott, Robert Falcon, 1868-1912
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Album 1, p.318.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to E. P. Oldfield, Torquay, Feb. 4, 1910; 10x8; Scott, Robert Falcon, 1868-1912
    Typed L.S. 1p. (see Album 2, p.91.) Thanks for money toward the British Antarctic expedition of 1910. Not found April, 2011.
  - Letter to Noble, Feb. 26, 1899; 7x4-1/2; Selours, Frederick Courteney, 1851-1917
    Worplesdon, A.L.S. 2p. (see Album 1, pp.250-251.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [John Thomas] Quekett, Jan. 21, 1860; 7x4; Setheby, H E
    A.L.S. 4p. (see Albums...; 1777-1917. Vol. IV, p.26.) Concerning minerals.
  - Autograph., 2-1/2x3-1/2; Simpson, James Young, Sir, 1811-1870
    A.D.S. 1p. (see Album 2, p.107.) Removed from a letter.
  - Letter to ----, May 11; 6x4-1/2; Smith, Benjamin Leigh, 1828-
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Albums. ...; 1777-1917. Vol. VI, p.62.) Thanks for publication.
  - Letter to Edm[und] Balfour, Oct. 9, 1880; 9x7; Smith, Goldwin, 1823-1910
    Oxford, A.L.S. 1p. (see Albums...; 1777-1917. Vol. IV, p.22.) Business.
  - Letter to ----, Feb. 23; 7x4-1/2; Spence, William, 1783-1860
    A.L.S. 3p. (see Albums ...; 1777-1917. Vol. IV, p.28.) Business. Refers to Richard Owen.
  - Letter to Sir Henry Thompson, Nov. 18, 1891; 7x4-1/2; Spencer, Herbert, 1820-1903
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Album 1, pp.175-176.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Lady Anne Wilbraham, Aug. 27, 1827; Stanley, Edward Smith, 13th Earl of Derby, 1775-1851
  - Letter to [Charles E.] Luard, Oct. 12, 1875; 7x4-1/2; Stokes, George Gabriel, 1819-1903
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 1p. (see Album 2, p.103.) Corrects and error.
  - Letter to John Quekett, April 26, 1859; 7x4-1/2; Story-Maskelyne, Nevil, 1823-1911
    British Museum, A.L.S. 3p.and end. (see Albums...; 1777-1917. Vol.IV, p.26.) Concerning minerals.
  - Card to Professor and Mrs. Turner, Dec. 30, 1911; 3-1/2x5-1/2; Struve, Hermann, 1854-1920
    Berlin, A.D.S. 1p.,add.,end. (see Albums...; 1777-1917. Vol. V, p.18.) Friendly note.
  - Letter to Mrs. Burrows, May 27; 6x4; Swanwick, Anna, 1813-1899
    A.L.S. 4p. (see Album 2, p.46.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Dickins, March 7, 1912; 7x4-1/2; Thiselton-Dyer, William T. (William Turner), 1843-1928
    Gloucester, A.L.S. 3p. (see Albums...; 1777-1917. Vol. V, p.24.) Friendly letter. Concerning Japan. Refers to the Royal society and to the Dictionary of national biography.
  - Letter to Sir Henry Thompson, April 4, 1893; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Thiselton-Dyer, William T. (William Turner), 1843-1928
    Kew, A.L.S. 1p. (see Album 1, pp.202-203.) Accepts invitation.
  - Letter to Mrs. James [?], April 2, 1895; 7x4-1/2; Thompson, Henry, Sir, 1820-1904
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Album 1, pp.183-184.) Sends autographs of various persons.
  - Autograph., 1777-1917; 1-1/2x4; Thompson, William, 1805-1852
    A.D.S. 1p. (see Albums...; Vol. II, p.20.) Removed from letter.
  - Letter to Leslie Thomson, May 8, 1911; 7x4; Thomson, John Millar, 1849-
    A.L.S. 2p. (see Albums...; 1777-1917. Vol. V, p.17.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Edward] Clodd, 7x4-1/2; Thomson, Joseph, 1858-1895
    Saturday. A.L.S. 2p. (see Albums ...; 1777-1917. Vol. IV, p.27.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Thomson, April 6, 1912; 9x7; Turner, H. H. (Herbert Hall), 1861-1930
    Oxford, A.L.S. 1p. (see Albums...; 1777-1917. Vol. V, p. 18.) Forwards autographs.
  - Letter to [John Thomas] Quekett, Jan. 15, 1851; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Ure, Andrew, 1778-1857
    A.L.S. 4p. (see Albums...; 1777-1917. Vol.IV, p.27.) Concerning an interesting case based on the chemical constituents of pepper. as analyzed with a microscope.
  - Note to ----., 3x4-1/2; Wells, Spencer, 1818-1897
    A.N.S. 1p. (see Album 1, pp.146-147.) Friendly note.
  - Letter to R[ichard] Owen, London, Feb. 9, 1839; 10x8; Whewell, William, 1794-1866
    Cambridge, A.L.S. 2p.and add. (see Albums...; 1777-1917. Vol.IV, p.8.) Friendly letter. Natural history. Refers to Cuvier.
  - Letter to John Milne, Jan. 30, 1912; 7x4-1/2; Woodward, Henry, 1832-1921
    A.L.S. 3p. (see Albums...; 1777-1917. Vol. V, p.24.) Concerning a publication on earthquakes. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to D. W. Mitchell, Aug. 31, 1855; 7x4-1/2; Yarrell, William, 1784-1856
    A.L.S. 1p. (see Albums ...; 1777-1917. Vol. V, p.9.) Business. Refers to Richard Owen.